http://ppi.searchy.net/privacy

ppi.searchy.net (home)
Copyright © 1999-2014 Penpal International, All rights reserved. - Privacy policy
Contact our Honeypot department if you are
desperate to get blacklisted.
Privacy policy of Penpal International
Account data
Penpal International only collects account information for usage by Penpal International. All account information besides email address is displayed publicly on the website of Penpal International.
Email addresses are only used by Penpal International to contact members to notify them of new messages on Penpal International by other members, important information messages regarding his/her account or important information about the website of Penpal International.
Cookies
Penpal International uses cookies for keeping members logged in after supplying login credentials.
Third-party cookies
Third-party vendors, including but not limited to Google, uses cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visit to Penpal International.
Googles use of DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based to a user bases on visits to Penpal International and/or other websites on the internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page.
Collection of digital information
When visiting Penpal International, the IP address used to access will be logged along with dates and times. This information is used for generating statistics.
Penpal International uses Google Analytics. Click here to learn
about the privacy policy of Google Analytics.
Changes to this privacy policy
The contents of this privacy policy may be altered at any time without notice.
